Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence-Hare Family, 1724-1965
  - E.M. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1957 January 30; No. 3800
  - Horace & E.M. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1956 February 25; No. 3800a
    Sorry to hear you broke your wrist. Thanks for sending suits.
  - Ellen Mary Hare to Esther, 1956 March 5; No. 3800b
    Advising of our leave of here and arrival in Philadelphia. Charles came up in uniform.
  - Hope to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1957 February 13; No. 3801
    Enjoyed your visit. Thank you for bed jacket. Charles and I saw movie "Giant" (terrible). Baby sweater for sister's baby.
  - Martha H. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1957 February 19; No. 3802
    Thank you for check. General correspondence.
  - E.M. Hare to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1957 March 4; No. 3803
    Trip here. Scenery.
  - Mary M. Watson to Miss Hare, 1957 March 11; No. 3804
    Sending recipe for Swansdown Angel Food Cake (enclosed).
  - Katharine to Miss Esther Hare, 1957 March 30; No. 3805
    Hotel, sights, travels, etc.
  - Miss Marion Powell to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1958 March 14; No. 3806
    Weather. Ill health in family.
  - Rosemary to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1958 November 6; No. 3807
    Thank you for silver "Paul Revere" bowl wedding gift.
  - Osse, Mark, Binney and Robin Meigs to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1959 November 25; No. 3808
    Gifts they would like to have.
  - Helen Hennings to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1960 January 1; No. 3809
    Thank you for check. New Year's wishes. My Christmas. Newspaper article "Miss Elizabeth Chew Dies in Family's Historic Mansion".
  - Marian Powell to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1960 February 5; No. 3810
    Thank you for calendar. Friendly letter.
  - Ellen Mary to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1960 June 30; No. 3811
    Outfitted boys with cowboy clothes. Riding.
  - Mrs. Charles Platt to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1960 September 18; No. 3812
    List of newer roses I like.
  - Robert Harbison to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1963 April 9; No. 3813
    Request for payment of bill.
  - Samuel Chew to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1965 May 7; No. 3814
    Invitation to wedding of daughter.
  - Mrs. Charles Platt to Miss Esther Hare, 1965 June 22; No. 3815
    Lucy had a stroke.
  - R. Tillinghast to Dr. Robert Hare, No. 3816
    October 2. Request to forward letter to Miss Anna Kane - father ill. (lock of hair enclosed)
  - Esther (daughter) to Hon. Horace Binney, No. 3817
    September 22. Anxious to see you. Horace studying regularly.
  - _______ to Mrs. Robert Hare, No. 3818
    Explaining she never mentioned a name and would not do anything disagreeable.
  - Horace Binney Hare to Mrs. Willing, No. 3819
    Thursday. Unable to accept invitation to dinner, but if can get Resident to substitute will meet the Misses Eustis' this evening.
  - Emily to Aunty, No. 3820
    December 9. About family.
  - Emily to Aunty, No. 3821
    November 21. Family news. Went to ball, but would rather go to musical entertainments. Has nursery governess for children.
  - Emily to Aunty, No. 3822
    October 19. Sorry to hear both had been ill and of Mrs. Stirling's death. Horace has had sciatica.
  - Emily to Aunty, No. 3823
    December 29. Christmas dinner with Mrs. T. Biddle and family celebrating Christmas in German way.
  - Emily to Aunty, No. 3824
    Family news and activities in Leipzig.
  - E. to Aunty, No. 3825
    November 25. Arrived this morning.
  - H.B. to Mrs. Esther C. Hare, No. 3826
    May 21. Will ride to Hoboken to dinner and get butter from Mrs. Cooper.
  - Mother to Mrs. E.C.B. Hare, No. 3827
    Cut out shirt - is it alright? If so, will cut out other. Rheumatism very bad.
  - Esther to Grandmama, No. 3828
    November 2. From Biarrits.
  - Horace Binney Hare to Mamma, No. 3829
    May 19. Ate sandwiches in New York. Went to New Haven by rail, then to Saybrook with father. Note from C.H.
  - Horace to Mrs. Hare, No. 3830
    July 30. Father has arrived from Canada and they expect to take steamer.
  - Horace to Mrs. Hare, No. 3831
    January 9. Plans for leaving Saturday.
  - H.B. to Mrs. E.C. Hare, No. 3832
    Saturday. Boy has rash and feel you should return home from New York.
  - H.B. to Mrs. Clark Hare, No. 3833
    June 13. Cholera.
  - Mother to Mrs. E.C.B. Hare, No. 3834
    Birthday note.
  - H.B.H. to Mamma, No. 3835
    Note asking to play with boats.
  - Mother to Mrs. E.C.B. Hare, No. 3836
    Thursday night. Note on returning son after visit and tells of love for him (Binney).
  - Mother to Mrs. Clark Hare, No. 3837
    Tuesday night. Papa wants pleasure of bringing Binney home. Will be in town for a few days.
  - Lill to Miss Esther C. Binney, No. 3838
    August 6. Papa sick, so you must find another escort to return home.
  - Lill (sister) to Miss Binney, No. 3839
    Thursday night. Mary sick. Mama went up. Wants books from library. Wants you to come home.
  - Lill to The Misses Binney, No. 3840
    Papa better. Had good-looking beaus visit - guess who?
  - Elizabeth Scott to Mrs. Esther C.B. Hare, No. 3841
    June 24. Thank you for gold pen.
  - Horace to Mother, No. 3842
    Tuesday. In ill health. Needs money.
  - C.H. to Mrs. Clark Hare, No. 3843
    August 28. About Horace's attack.
  - E.P.H. to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3844
    September 14. Was ill at Lake Mohawk. Now somewhere near Boston.
  - Horace to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3845
    December 29. Going to Newport tomorrow.
  - Horace to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3846
    December 30. About finding rooms. Saw cousin Sam.
  - Horace & Emily to Mrs. J.I.C. Hare, No. 3847
    April 7. Horace someplace in South for health. His condition. Asks for money and hat.
  - Horace & Emily to Mrs. J.I.C. Hare, No. 3848
    April 25. Check received. Health. Sat out under trees.
  - Horace Binney Hare to Mrs. Hare, No. 3849
    April 10. Somewhere in the South. No birds to shoot. Not having too good a time.
  - J.I.C.H. to Mrs. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3850
    Could not get cabins yesterday, so staying there on way to Palerno. Keep children studying.
  - R.H. Hare (brother) to Hon. Clark Hare, No. 3851
    September 24. Introducing Dr. Charles Carpenter.
  - R.H. Hare to Hon. Clark Hare, No. 3852
    February 28. About selling house on Chestnut St.
  - E. Beale to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3853
    Sunday. Thank you for photograph of yourself.
  - ______ to Clark Hare, No. 3854
    August 16. (PRIVATE) Benefit derived from water of White Sulphur Springs. A hopeless passion. Misunderstanding with Harry. Politics.
  - Emily to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3855
    April 10. Sightseeing. Children studying French and adults Italian. Desirous of having Esther painted by Gordigiani, but charges too high. Plans for either meeting children in England or at home.
  - Baby and Aunt Connie to Judge J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3856
    January 17. Child's letter.
  - Horace and Emily to Judge Hare, No. 3857
    April 8. In the South for ill health. Plans for returning home.
  - Emily and Horace to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3858
    April 13. Horace's health. Weather bad. Request for money.
  - Horace to Hon. J.I.C. Hare, No. 3859
    April 16. Feeling better with good weather. Need funds.
  - Andrew J. Reilly to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3860
    Pleasure of seeing Judge so well.
  - A.V. Dicey to J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3861
    July 28. Anxious to meet you. Telegraph your plans. Invitation to dinner.
  - Clark Hare, No. 3862
    Essay - the United States Government, military rule or anarchy. Another arguing right or wrong of civilized nations seizing lands belonging to barbarious ones. Ancient Romans - peace and war.
  - ______ to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3863
    Specifications for schooner equipment, provisions, etc.
  - Esther to Hon. J.I. Clark Hare, No. 3864
    September 2. Unfavorable impression of Mr. Balfour. See King daily. Going to Paris and will be home soon.
  - Emily to Dr. H.B. Hare, No. 3865
    May 28. Couldn't go on picnic - rain.
  - Emily to Dr. H.B. Hare, No. 3866
    May 15 - Went to Capitol - Senate room.
  - Emily to Dr. Horace B. Hare, No. 3867
    February 21. Carnival - a great "fizzle". General news.
  - Captain Hare's action in the Army, No. 3868
    May 20. Against a rioting crowd in gaining possession of arms for United States Army.
  - J.A. Barry to Captain H.B. Hare, No. 3869
    Letter of praise as troop commander.
  - Emily to Horace Binney Hare, M.D., No. 3870
    January 8. Returning home on Tuesday after taking care of ill Mother.
  - Emily to Dr. H.B. Hare, No. 3871
    February 5. Bring Sam to tea.
  - Emily to Horace Binney Hare, No. 3872
    August 17. Roy improving. Minnie Hare engaged to Sussex Davis.
  - Emily to Dr. Horace Binney Hare, No. 3873
    June 23. She and mother went to your mother and father's where things were sad. Went to Mrs. Crawford's where little boys were speaking "pieces". Your Mother "broke down" saying a prayer for you.
  - Mr. & Mrs. F. Francis Fisher, Mr. Brinton Coxe, Miss Maria M. Fisher to Dr. & Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3874
    An event at St. Peter's Church (probably a wedding).
  - Emily to H.B. Hare, M.D., No. 3875
    July 20. War between France and Russia. Mr. Robeson and Andrew sailed over. Food bad, but bathing lovely.
  - Emily to Horace B. Hare, No. 3876
    December 28. Trying to comfort Mamma. Feels bad about Eddie going so far from home. Instructions to Mrs. McFall to make dress.
  - Emily to Horace Binney Hare, M.D., No. 3877
    August 4. Went to church. Your mother visited. Baby well, but not Roy. Sad about leaving here. Visited Chestnut Hill.
  - Emily to Horace Binney Hare, M.D., No. 3878
    August 14. Roy improving. Went to city and ward for Philadelphia - "smells". Weather hot. Charlie doing well at mine, but Maria ill.
  - Emily to Horace B. Hare, M.D., No. 3879
    January 3. Not necessary to come for her. Visited Aunt Emily. Teaching Katy. Feeling wretchedly gloomy.
  - Emily to Horace, No. 3880
    December 31. Trunk has not come. Request for beef tea, money and that you write Charlie.
  - Emily to Dr. Horace B. Hare, No. 3881
    February 23. Mamma not at all well, but am coming home. Last night of carnival a beautiful sight.
  - Emily to Dr. H.B. Hare, No. 3882
    August 3. Can't understand why spending so much time in London, and afraid the war will prevent traveling in Europe. Social events. Went sailing. Does not want to return to Cedar Grove. Roy walking by chairs. Request for stockings from London and underbodies, petticoats, silk stockings, cravats and lace shawl from Paris.
  - William H. Hare (cousin) to H.B. Hare, M.D., No. 3883
    Congratulations on securing position in hospital created by vacancy of Dr. Thomson.
  - Emily to Dr. H.B. Hare, No. 3884
    May 14. Leaving home - journey to Washington.
  - Horace to Miss E.P. Beale, No. 3885
    Making "date" for 5, and if you can get Maria to put off trip until Friday, will accompany you.
  - ______ to Emily, No. 3886
    (part of a letter) Behaving badly, feet hurt, talk about friends, and invitation to visit.
  - Mother to Emily, No. 3887
    July 13. Trying to comfort. Connie and Kate. Charlie and Maria want them to visit. Plans for the summer. Horse for Eddie. July 21. Advising to plan for trip to Europe in Spring and go away a while this summer. About cottage near you.
  - ______ to Emily, No. 3888
    Tuesday evening. Writing poetry. John Hoffman and Helen. Sandy. Come Saturday and bring Bessie.
  - Maria to Emily, No. 3889
    May 18. (part of a letter). Expecting quantity of cousins and relations from the South. Afraid soon will have to give up room and old dresses to them.
  - Maria to Emily, No. 3890
    June 23. Visited Lily Wister. Relating all the "gossip".
  - Maria to Emmie, No. 3891
    Thursday evening. "Hurt" at not receiving letters. Sandy will be here, so you must come.
  - Maria to Emily, No. 3892
    Wednesday evening. Friendly letter.
  - Maria to Em, No. 3893
    Monday evening. Went riding today and saddle slipped over horse's head when he stepped in swamp and I landed floundering in mud.
  - Maria to "Dearest", No. 3894
    Thursday evening. Visit to Chestnut Hill.
  - A.S. Biddle to Miss Emily Beale, No. 3895
    Monday. Sending flowers left from centerpiece.
  - N.P.T. (uncle) to Emily, No. 3896
    July 18. Was pleased with account of Boston trip and wants to hear about Provisence, Cousin Eliza and Cape May news.
  - R.T. Willing to Miss Emily P. Beale, No. 3897
    December 19. Enclosing excuse to school for failure to learn Latin lesson and being late.
  - Horace to Miss Emily P. Beale, No. 3898
    Wednesday afternoon. Will be back Saturday.
  - Maria to "My dear Friend", No. 3899
    August 25. Friendly letter, about her love.
  - Maria to Em, No. 3900
    Tuesday evening. About "secrets".
  - M.M.F. to Emily, No. 3901
    August 8. Sophey ill, needs sea air, so is at Atlantic City. Request to get rooms at Narragansett for Helen.
  - M.M.F. to "My dearest", No. 3902
    Saturday afternoon. "Raging headache". No chance M.J.I.'s coming. If Sandy comes will write again.
  - Maria Alverthorpe to Emily, No. 3903
    Tuesday. Come Thurday and spend night - have to talk. Get and bring letter (secret and cause of much excitement).
  - Horace to Miss E.P. Beale, No. 3904
    Thank you for gloves.
  - Horace to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3905
    Thursday. At wedding. Will be home Saturday.
  - Horace to E., No. 3906
    Monday. Ask "Mep" to go to theatre and decide on night and theatre.
  - Evelyn Wadsworth to Mrs. Horace Hare, No. 3907
    October 1. Sending blanket for baby.
  - N.P.T. (uncle) to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3908
    Details of a visit from your Mamma, Constance and Katey. Unbearable heat.
  - Horace to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3909
    Thursday evening. With Julian at farm at Emmonton.
  - M.H.C. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3910
    Thursday evening. Enthusiastic about Edinburgh and sorry you didn't come to enjoy the sightseeing. Buying suits for Francis and little Horace.
  - M.M.F. (cousin) to Emily, No. 3911
    October 10. Shopping and driving in Paris.
  - ______ to Emily, No. 3912
    April 25. (part of a letter) About new house. Couldn't get lingerie and can't bring anything with her for others.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3913
    Thursday. Tells of catching sailfish and picture of fish enclosed. Dr. Jack is there and looked him over and thought him in good shape.
  - Emily to Granny, No. 3914
    November 28. Having delightful time. Visited Aunt Swift and Aunt Crosby.
  - Horace to Mother, No. 3915
    May 20. Saw Willing yesterday morning. "Bewildering" life, but doesn't seem silly now that it is the only way of preserving it.
  - Emily ? to ______, No. 3916
    About boat "The Venture".
  - E.P.H. to ______, No. 3917
    "draft" of a letter telling of Mother's death and one to Truxtun Beale on the death of his son killed in battle.
  - E.P.H. to ______, No. 3918
    August 8. Sort of dreary vacation. Boys off on cruise. Driving, sailing, reading, etc.
  - Dr. Bruce Gill to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3919
    Prescription for X-ray of both hips.
  - Cass to Emily, No. 3920
    November 22. A note with roses and forget-me-nots while ill.
  - Mother to Emily, No. 3921
    September 5. Became ill when Esther arrived. Description of many flowers and food received. Visitors. Connie's and Esther's social events. Fears not able to go to mountains, but may go to hospital.
  - Emily (niece) to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3922
    Thank you for handkerchiefs.
  - Cass to Emily, No. 3923
    December 14. Thank you for clothes. Invitation to visit.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3924
    July 26 and 27. Sick all week. Had to call night clerk to rub away extreme pain. Joined "Country Club" for family. Social events. Comments on Ned McLean's marriage and Mrs. Van Rensalner's son demanding $5000 or "blow her head off".
  - Emily (niece) to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3925
    Tuesday. Thank you for china.
  - Robert J. Hare Powel to Mrs. Hare, No. 3926
    July 5. Comparing Mrs. Hare to comet. Note sent on its way.
  - Lucy Thorndike to Mrs. Horace Hare, No. 3927
    May 27. Letter from Winnie's Mother in appreciation of her in-laws attending wedding, and how pleased she is with them.
  - Emily to Mamma, No. 3928
    March 16. Sent poem. Enjoyed the lunch yesterday. Comments on your falling down stairs.
  - Katherine Welling (Cass) to Emily, No. 3929
    June 20. Expresses a need for each other. Enjoying the summer and looking forward to visit at Harford in Winter.
  - Cass to Emily, No. 3930
    May 13. Expressing her sadness in Emily's (Bebe) death.
  - Louise Endicott to Mrs. Hare, No. 3931
    Thank you for pansies. Will not be able to attend tea tomorrow.
  - Willing Hare to Mama, No. 3932
    Note telling about things at home.
  - C. Willing (Uncle Charlie) to Emmie, No. 3933
    Trying to improve theirselves with reading.
  - Willing Hare to Mama, No. 3934
    Child's note to mother.
  - M.M. to Mrs. Hare, No. 3935
    Wednesday. Garden Club meeting transferred to Mrs. Newhall's.
  - Ellen Mary Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3936
    Thursday. Sympathy note on Mrs. Bayard's death.
  - Auntie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3937
    January 19. A letter of consolation.
  - Maria to Emily, No. 3938
    February, March and April. Maria's expenses for "feeding" family for three months.
  - ______ to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3939
    Broadcast speech on trespassing.
  - Tessie Biddle to Emily, No. 3940
    Monday. Offer to take other children during Roy's illness.
  - J.I.C. Clark Hare to Emily, No. 3941
    December 16. About finances.
  - Library Company of Philadelphia to Emily P. Hare, No. 3942
    Transfer form.
  - Auntie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3943
    November 18. Offer to keep baby while you go to St. Thomas, and a letter trying to comfort in this time of so much sorrow and anguish.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3944
    Sunday. Inside of house to be done before you come home (details of work done).
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3945
    Sunday. Description of trip, hotel and people, and how civilization has moved out.
  - Daughter (Esther) to Mamma, No. 3946
    Saturday night. Journey with Grandma and Grandpapa. Bored, but really feels like she's needed as nurse and companion for them to Palm Beach.
  - W.L. Hope to Mrs. Hare, No. 3947
    July 31. Request you write from Bath.
  - Horace to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3948
    October 19. Returning home.
  - Katherine Welling (Cass) to Emily, No. 3949
    July 27. At a lovely mountain spot. News of Molly and Bebe. Drawing of their new "Summer" house.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3950
    Friday. Thinks it wise you do not attempt lake trip, but he is going to take it. Asks Esther to get leather portfolio in Florence.
  - Esther to Mother, No. 3951
    July 16. Visiting H. and E.M. in Europe. Detailed day of baby's (E.M.) schedule.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3952
    Tuesday. Boat trip to Palermo.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3953
    Monday. Visit in Palermo.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace Hare, No. 3954
    Wednesday. Plans for Holy Week in Rome to go to cermonies at churches, and to see the Cardinal and Pope. Description of view from hotel room. Visits, guests and sights. Purchased lace and silks. Make appointment in Rome for coiffeur.
  - Truxtun Hare, Jr. (grandson) to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3955
    Friday. Glad to be home from France, but really lived a French life while there. Thank you for letter and check.
  - Anna Chew to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3956
    May 23. Best wishes for trip abroad.
  - Mary Chew to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3957
    July 15. Thank you for your sympathy on Sam's death.
  - Maimy to Emily, No. 3958
    Sunday. Invitation for you and Esther to visit in July at Newport, but not together as only one spare room.
  - Maimy to Emily, No. 3959
    June 25. Would like to have you and Esther together if you will share one and only guest room. Plans for the visit and request you telegraph if you can come.
  - Mrs. M. Maxwell Fox to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3960
    Calling card.
  - Mrs. Holmes to Mrs. Hare, No. 3961
    February 27. Invitation to luncheon.
  - R.T.W. (aunt) to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3962
    April 25.(Written by aunt who raised her). Ill with heart attack. Very displeased with remarks made to outsiders on family matters.
  - Maimy to Emily, No. 3963
    Sunday morning. Invitation to lunch.
  - M.M.C. to Emily, No. 3964
    Wednesday. Request to be Patroness for course of lectures on forestry.
  - Randolph to Mrs. Hare, No. 3965
    Monday. Cannot be at "post" this afternoon. Children enjoying gifts.
  - Mother to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3966
    May 31. On return to Bloomingdale. So busy. Baby. Maria's sewing. Katie "fixed up" for May Ball. Quite ill with cold. Went to church one time since return and felt so welcomed by friends. Ned Pendleton divorced and married again.
  - M.A.B. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3967
    August 30. Mixup in plans of meeting place in Europe.
  - Emily to Mamma Hare, No. 3968
    August 14. Esther will get little case for you. Particularly enjoyed opera in Bayreuth.
  - Mamma Hare to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3969
    Your Mother's and my plans to visit you in Georgia. John, the coachman, ran over a child's leg, but resulted only in bad bruise.
  - Horace to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3970
    Good Friday. Description of hotel, rooms and food - not a place for women. (part of a letter).
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3971
    April 23. Letter to Mother.
  - Willing to Mamma, No. 3972
    Wednesday. Visiting the Livingstons. Going to steam down Hudson. While riding to call at Astor's, vicious dog tried to bite, and avoiding it, broke wheel.
  - Willing to Mrs. Hare, No. 3973
    March 14. Child's letter to sister.
  - Harriet Hare McClellan to Mrs. Hare, No. 3974
    February 7. Tells about the play, Phantom party, Fred and Lola Prime, Hope Powel, and the birth of your niece.
  - Emily Power Hare to ______, No. 3975
    Childhood story (Bloomingdale mentioned). Lived with Grandmother in country and Aunt in city.
  - C.W.H. to Mamma, No. 3976
    May 8. Bicycle riding. Asks that you take trip with Truxtun.
  - Willing to Mamma, No. 3977
    Sunday. (part of a letter). Fishing with Grandpapa, and went for tarpon.
  - Willing to Mamma, No. 3978
    Friday. About the Wrights. Mrs. Wright wants to meet you in Paris.
  - E.C.H. to Emily, No. 3979
    February 18. Ill and left without a laundress.
  - Arthur Little to Mrs. Hare, No. 3980
    Invitation to walk.
  - Mother (M.A.B.) to Emily, No. 3981
    July 28. Home news. Received letter from Ned and Maria describing the falling of the bell tower of St. Mark's in Venice. Playing in Mr. Hare's tent with Hope and Lena. Henrietta Brown's wedding. Enjoying staying with the Hare's, but must leave when heat comes. Wishes you could see Mark Twain - Charlie like him so much.
  - Mother to Emily, No. 3982
    Wednesday night. Thanking you for two birds (if they were from you). Had hoped to see you at tea, but was kept later at Katy's than expected.
  - Oliver Perry Smith to Mrs. H.B. Hare, No. 3983
  - Mother to Emily, No. 3984
    September 29. Plans for visiting for Rydie's wedding. Concern for Katy.
  - T.H. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3985
    August 8. Had a delightful time at Rye Beach.
  - Esther to Mamma, No. 3986
    July 4. Tested colt before going for a drive by setting off fire crackers under his nose. "Duckie's" prizes for sports. Dinner and fun last night. New clothes. Going to fireworks tonight.
  - E. Rucellair to Mrs. Hare, No. 3987
    Friday evening. Invitation to see you and daughter.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3988
    December 10. From school. Mr. Thayer says he will stop Eleven Dinner - somehow think you wrote him about it. Coming home next week.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, No. 3989
    Wednesday. November 29. From school.
  - Mary Powel to Emily, No. 3990
    Monday. Letter of comfort in sorrow.